

export const data = [

    {
        question:'I __',
        choise:[
            'play',
            'plays'
            
        ],
        answer: 'play'

    },
	 {
        question:'My friend ___',
        choise:[
            'eat',
            'eats'
            
        ],
        answer: 'eats'

    },
 {
        question:'The boys ___',
        choise:[
            'sing',
            'sings'
            
        ],
        answer: 'sing'

    },
    
{
        question:'You ___',
        choise:[
            'talk',
            'talks'
            
        ],
        answer: 'talk'

    },
{
        question:'My aunt and you ___',
        choise:[
            'swim',
            'swims'
            
        ],
        answer: 'swim'

    },
{
        question:'He ___',
        choise:[
            'comes',
            'come'
            
        ],
        answer: 'comes'

    },
{
        question:'My cat ___',
        choise:[
            'run',
            'runs'
            
        ],
        answer: 'runs'

    },
	{
        question:'Your wife ___',
        choise:[
            'watch',
            'watches'
            
        ],
        answer: 'watches'

    },
	{
        question:'His brother ___',
        choise:[
            'study',
            'studies'
            
        ],
        answer: 'studies'

    },
	{
        question:'My sister and I___',
        choise:[
            'cooks',
            'cook'
            
        ],
        answer: 'cook'

    },
{
        question:'My father___',
        choise:[
            'wash',
            'washes'
            
        ],
        answer: 'washes'

    },
	{
        question:'You ___',
        choise:[
            'work',
            'works'
            
        ],
        answer: 'work'

    },
	{
        question:'She ___',
        choise:[
            'goes',
            'go'
            
        ],
        answer: 'goes'

    },
	{
        question:'He and Mark___',
        choise:[
            'do',
            'does'
            
        ],
        answer: 'do'

    },
	{
        question:'He ___',
        choise:[
            'does',
            'do'
            
        ],
        answer: 'does'

    },
	{
        question:'My son ____',
        choise:[
            'sleep',
            'sleeps'
            
        ],
        answer: 'sleeps'

    },
	{
        question:'Her bike____',
        choise:[
            'have',
            'has'
            
        ],
        answer: 'has'

    },
	{
        question:'Cows____',
        choise:[
            'have',
            'has'
            
        ],
        answer: 'have'

    },
	{
        question:'John____',
        choise:[
            'try',
            'tries'
            
        ],
        answer: 'tries'

    },
	{
        question:'My friend____',
        choise:[
            'say',
            'says'
            
        ],
        answer: 'says'

    },
	{
        question:'I____',
        choise:[
            'read',
            'reads'
            
        ],
        answer: 'read'

    },
	{
        question:'You ____',
        choise:[
            'read',
            'reads'
            
        ],
        answer: 'read'

    },
	{
        question:'He____',
        choise:[
            'read',
            'reads'
            
        ],
        answer: 'reads'

    },
	{
        question:'She____',
        choise:[
            'reads',
            'read'
            
        ],
        answer: 'reads'

    },
	{
        question:'It____',
        choise:[
            'read',
            'reads'
            
        ],
        answer: 'reads'

    },
	{
        question:'We____',
        choise:[
            'read',
            'reads'
            
        ],
        answer: 'read'

    },
	{
        question:'You____',
        choise:[
            'reads',
            'read'
            
        ],
        answer: 'read'

    },{
        question:'They____',
        choise:[
            'read',
            'reads'
            
        ],
        answer: 'read'

    },
	
	


]

